ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Public Investing Policy-Edmond G. Brown, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  California Governor's Report
- Burlington Industries Inc, 1978-1981 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Business/Labor Working Group (Box 85, Folder 18)
  NYC Jobs/Economic regeneration report
- C Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Canada Economic Data, Correspondence, Etc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  Reports; Articles
- Canadian-American Committee, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Canadian-American Committee-Meeting, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  Chicago, March 27
- Canadian-American Committee, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  Meeting Agendas; Reports; Memos
- Pennsylvania Candidates-1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  Materials and Correspondence regarding electoral candidates
- Casino Control Commission, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Cannon Mills, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  Articles, Memos; Takeover by David Murdock
- Carlin's, 1979-1980 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  Memos regarding Amalgamated Insurance Fund
- Citizens for Tax Justice, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  First Annual Report
- Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition. [Folder 1 of 3], 1981 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition. [Folder 2 of 3], 1980-1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition. [Folder 3 of 3], 1978-1983 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- City of Hope, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  Memos; Materials; Morty Bahr Dinner
- "Clean Air", 1977-192 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Clippings, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Clippings, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Clothing Manufacturer's Association, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  National Agreement with ACTWU; Memos
- Clothing Manufacturer's Association, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Clothing Manufacturer's Association-Pension/Insurance Committee, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  November 9, 1981 Memo
- Community Council of Greater NY-Ad-hoc Committee on Social Security, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  Memos; Materials; News Articles; Reports
- Social Security-Articles/Reports, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Community Labor Organizing Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Cone Mills, 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  Memos; Report on company
- Congressional Study Group on International Trade and Economics, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  Correspondence; Research Report
- Contributions-Priority. [Folder 1 of 3], 1981 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  September-December
- Contributions-Priority. [Folder 2 of 3], 1981 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  May-August,
- Contributions-Priority. [Folder 3 of 3], 1981 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  January-April
- Committee on Political Education-AFL-CIO, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Committee on Political Education-AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Corbin, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  July 26 Memo
- Corporate Campaign-Ray Rogers, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Corporate Data Exchange, Inc, 1978-1982 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Corporate Democracy, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  "The Case for a Corporate Democracy Act of 1980" Report
- Cost of Living Adjustment, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  Pay Schedules; Inflation/Growth report
- Council On Economic Priorities, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  November Newsletter
- Council on the Economy of New York City, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  Article; Correspondence
- Council on Foreign Relations, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  Correspondence; Survey results
- D Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  Reports; Data; Correspondence
- Darlington, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  Documents regarding 1950's Back Pay
- Democracy Project, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  September 1981-September 1982 Annual Report
- Democratic National Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor (ERISA), 1982 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- District 65, 1977-1981 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  Hofstra University
- E Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Eagle Clothes, 1977-1981 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Education Department, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Engineering Department, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1973-1980 (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Ethical Culture Society, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Export Trading Companies, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  Report on US Exports
- F Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 27)
- Federation for American Immigration Reform, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 28)
- Film Fund-Labor Day, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 29)
- Finance Department, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 30)
- Finance Department, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 31)
- Flat-Rate Tax Proposals, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  Citizens for Tax Justice
- Foundation for Independent Video and Film, Inc, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 33)
- Frontlash, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 34)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 35)
- G Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  October 26-28
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  April
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  February meeting; Consolidation of other folders
- Greeting, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  Constitutional Convention Call
- Greetings, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  Convention correspondence
- Convention 1981-Session Transcriptions (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Convention 1981-Committees (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Convention 1981-Correspondence (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Convention 1981-Guests, Thank-you letters (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Convention 1981-Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Convention 1981-Resolutions (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Convention 1981-Speech File (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Convention 1981-Voting (Box 88, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  September 28-29, 1983, Tarrytown, N.Y.
- Organizing, 1981-1983 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Trust for Balanced Investment, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO 1983 Convention-Resolution Requests (Box 88, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board-Resolution Requests, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  September 29.
- General Executive Board-Research Material, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board-ACTWU-Political Action Committees, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board-Administratorships, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board-Referendum Election on Constitutional Amendments, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board-Resolutions, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board August-Tarryton Hilton, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  August 1-5
- General Executive Board August-Research Department Material, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board August-Printed Material, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board August-Financial, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board August-Insurance, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board August-Imports and Trade, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board August-Agenda, Minutes, Constitution, etc, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board-April, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board-April-Election Procedures Convention, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board-April-Imports, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board-April-Open Administratorships, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board-December-Meeting, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 36)
- General Executive Board-December-Print Material, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 37)
- GEB Meeting-August 1981 (Box 88, Folder 38)
- General Executive Board-December-Research Material, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board-December-Agenda, Minutes, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board-Form Letters, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board-July-Constitution, Minutes, etc, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board-July-Financial, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board-July-Research Material, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board-July-Research Material, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board-July-Organizing, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board-March-Meeting, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  March 8-13, San Juan, Puerto Rico
- General Executive Board-March-Research Reports, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board-May Meeting, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  May 20-21
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  Financial Records,Remarks, Correspondence, Reports, etc
- Industrial Areas Foundation, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF-Technology, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  Orenas, Sweden Summit
- ITGLWF-Presidium-Sweden, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  September; English and Swedish
- ITGLWF-Correspondence, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  Memos; Letters; Finances, English/Spanish
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Jewish Labor Committee-Convention, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Jobs, Peace, and Freedom March, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  August 27
- Baltimore Joint Board-Nocella Charges, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- Toronto Trip, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  June 14-18,
- ITGLWF Presdium, 1982-1983 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- M.I.T. Report-Worker participation and American Unions, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  Kochan, Katz, Mower. Full size binder, not in folder.
- Third Canadian Conference-ACTWU, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  May 9-11, English, French
- Labor Day Parade, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Legal Department, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Manhattan Industries, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  Correspondence regarding imports and outside contracts
- ACTWU Memos, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  Elections, Amalgamated Bank, Department of Labor, Retirement Plans
- Administratorships, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- IUD Conference on National Industrial Policy, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  July 21
- IUD-Conference on Technology, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  Washington D.C. - September
- IUD Convention, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  Detroit, MI, October 1982
- IUD Convention, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  Atlantic City, New Jersey; Delegate list, Schedule
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund-Blue Papers, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  (Cotfund)-Meeting Agendas, Minutes
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund-Blue Papers, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Fund-Blue Papers, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  Meeting minutes, Agendas
- American Arbitration Association, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Blue Copies, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Blue Copies, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  July-September
- Blue Copies, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  April-June
- Blue Copies, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  January-March
- British-North American Committee, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Canadian-American Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- General Contributions, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Contributions-Political, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Contributions-Priority, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Contributions-Special Priority, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Contributions-General, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Contributions-Priority, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Contributions-Special Priority, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- NAACP Legal Defense Fund, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- OSHA, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  Reports; Communications
- General Pending, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Irving Alter Pending, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Irving Alter Pending, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Burt Beck-Pending, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Burt Beck Pending, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Gary Ferraris-Pending, 1982-1983 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Dave Dyson Pending, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Finance Department-Pending, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Legal Department-Pending, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Legal Pending, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Vera Miller-Pending, 1981-1983 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  Memos, Correspondence, Reports
- Amalgamated Bank-Ed Katz-Pending, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  Articles; Correspondence
- Ed Katz-Pending, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Harvey Sigelbaum-Pending, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Harvey Sigelbaum-Pending, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, Memos
- George Solomons-Pending. [Folder 1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  1981-June 1982. Memos; Correspondence; Reports
- George Solomons-Pending. [Folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  July-December 1982. Correspondence, Reports, Memos
- ILGWU Annual Report, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  Department of Labor Form LM-2.
- George Solomons, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- George Solomons, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- George Solomons-Pending, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  Memos; Reports; Member lists
- Research, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  Research reports, memos regarding same
- Resumes, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  Resumes and Letters of Recommendation
- UNA-USA, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  Reports, articles, publications, letters, memos
- UNA-USA-Economic Policy Council, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  Reports of EPC
- Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1982-1983 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  Proceedings of the Board, July 1982 to June 1983
- AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO IUD Publications, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- California Labor Federation-AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Central Labor Council-AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  San Bernardino, California
- Indiana State AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Maine AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Michigan State AFL-CIO, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Texas AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Political Action Committee, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- IUD Convention, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- IUD AFL-CIO Conference, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Alabama Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Arkansas Southwest Regional Joint Board., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Capital District Joint Board, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Cleaners and Dyers Joint Board, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Eastern Shore Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- El Paso, Texas Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Georgia Joint Board, 1972-174 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Gloves Cities Area Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board, 1971-1974 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Laundry Workers Joint Board, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Lehigh Valley, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Miami, Florida, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Mayfield District Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Minnesota Joint Board, 1971-1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Mississippi Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Local 169-New York, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  Correspondence, Financial Records
- Local 340-New York, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- New England Regional Office, 1971-1975 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- New Orleans Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board, 1971-1975 (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Baltimore Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Boston Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Central States Joint Board, 1973-1976 (Box 95, Folder 27)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board., 1973-1976 (Box 95, Folder 29)
- Local 198, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 30)
- Locals, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  Correspondence, Listing of Locals
- Local 324, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 32)
- Local 4-New York, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 33)
- Local 125-Newhaven, Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 34)
- Local 126-Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1972-1976 (Box 95, Folder 35)
- Local 87-Duluth, Minnesota, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 36)
- Local 158-New York City, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 37)
- Local 195-Newark, New Jersey, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 38)
- Local 208-Vineland, New Jersey, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 39)
- North Alabama Area Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 40)
- Northern California Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 41)
- Northwest Regional Joint Board, 1971-1973 (Box 95, Folder 42)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 43)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 44)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 45)
- Richmond, Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 46)
  Katherine Turner, Correspondence
- Puerto Rico, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 47)
  Newspaper, Correspondence
- Rochester Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 48)
- Scranton-Wilkes Barre Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 49)
  Newspaper articles, Correspondence
- Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, and Sportswear Joint Board, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 50)
  Report, Correspondence
- South Bend-Indiana, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 51)
- Southern California Joint Board-L.A., 1972 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- South Eastern Regional Joint Office, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- St. Louis Joint Board, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Southwest Regional Office-Dallas, 1958-1972 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Toronto Joint Board, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board, 1970-1972 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Winnipeg, Canada, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Locals, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Housing Corporation, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Trust and Savings Bank, Chicago, Illinois, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance-Chicago, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Arrearages, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  Financial Records and Reports
- Union Square Real Estate/Property, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Cotton Garment, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Scranton-Wilkes Barre Joint Board, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, and Sportswear Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- South Alabama Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Southern California Joint Board, L.A., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- South Eastern Regional Office, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Convention 1981-Committees (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Toronto Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  English, Yiddish Newspaper articles
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Cotton Garment, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company-Chicago, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Trust and Savings-Chicago, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Union Square Reality Corporation, 1970-1973 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  Records regarding various Union Square Properties
- Hyman Weiss, Union Square Reality, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  Litigation involving Weiss.
- Union Square Reality Corporation, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 24)
- Brennan Vs Union Square Reality Corporation, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 25)
- Union Square-Electrical Repairs, 1969-1972 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Employee Federal Credit Union, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO COPE Meetings, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Committee on Public Education, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Union Label and Service Trades Dept, NYS, AFL-CIO, 1974-1975 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Washington D.C., 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Union Label & Service Trades-AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO News, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, Washington D.C., 1975 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Virginia AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Washington D.C., 1975 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO IUD Publications, 1976-1977 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 19)
- APEC-Washington D.C., 1977 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- South Caroline Labor Council-AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 21)
- COPE -AFLCIO Subscriptions, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 22)
- Union Label Convention, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Councils-(Misc), 1973 (Box 98, Folder 25)
- Canadian Labor Congress, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 26)
- Arkansas State AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 27)
- Colorado Labor Council-AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Missouri State Labor Council-AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 29)
- North Carolina-AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Tenth Constitutional Convention-AFL CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  Bal Harbour, Florida, October 18
- Industrial Union Department, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 32)
- Industrial Union Department Convention, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  July 8th
- California State Confederation-AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 34)
- AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 35)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence-January-June, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 36)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence-July-December, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 37)
- "Save our Jobs" Rally, I.U.D-AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 38)
  Blue Envelope with enclosed Documents
- Industrial Union Department-Records and Correspondence, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Councils (Miscellaneous), 1972 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO News, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO COPE Conferences, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Canadian Labor Congress, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Mgrs, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Workers, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Richmond, Virginia Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Scranton-Wilkes Barre Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Clean Air acts, 1977-1982 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  Materials; Memos; Legislation; Reports
- Southern California Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Xerox Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  NLRB Case; Correspondence; Articles; Reports
- Southeastern Clothing Regional Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Saint Louis Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- United Farm Workers-Texas Boycott, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1974-1978 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company-Financial Records, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  Weekly Financial Statements
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company-Financial Records, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- Clothing Retirement Plan, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- Union Square Reality Corporation, 1973-1978 (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Cotton Garment, 1974-1978 (Box 99, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance-Chicago, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 26)
- Otis Elevator Company, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 27)